nightingale.com 2015-05-30

# Privacy and Security

## **Privacy Policy**

The Internet, Privacy and Nightingale-Conant The Internet contains a wealth of information. Unfortunately, it may also contain personal details about you that you don't want everyone to know. For example, your real name (lots of people on the Internet use aliases, alter egos or nicknames), street address, phone number, or e-mail address. Also, when you go online, sites you visit may be gathering information about you without your knowledge.

Upon your first visit to Nightingale-Conant, Nightingale-Conant sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data. In no way does this tell us that you're "Bob Smith." 

Nightingale-Conant has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. For example, when ordering products and services through our Web site, after your initial registration, your preferences pertaining to shipping and billing locations are remembered by our system. This way you don't have to tell us over and over again where you want your products sent. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the Nightingale-Conant Web site that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to Nightingale-Conant always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Most browses are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Nightingale-Conant Web site may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

Nightingale-Conant's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Nightingale-Conant's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. We reserve the right at our discretion to make changes to this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.

## **Site Security**

Nightingale-Conant's policy on our wholly controlled and operated Internet site is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. Nightingale-Conant will never willfully disclose individually identifiable information about its customers to any third party without first receiving that customer's permission. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so.

Nightingale-Conant shares information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. However, in most cases, we talk about our users in aggregate, not as individuals. For example, we will say Nightingale-Conant's audience is x percent females and y percent males. This data is used to customize Nightingale-Conant content and advertising for our users.

There are cases where Nightingale-Conant may ask you for personal information such as your name or address. We do this when you register to our site or make a product or service purchase. When we intend to use your personal information, we tell you up front. This way you can decide whether you want to give us the information or not. For example, we may want to send you product or service announcements via e-mail or regular mail at your request. In case you change your mind or some personal information may change (such as your billing or shipping address), you may easily correct, update or remove the personal data you give us by using our Account Status Area.
